

PR, Social Media, Brand Development and Digital Marketing

Phone 214-300-9808

Twitter
@JustBBarnett

GitHub @JustBBarnett

Profile

B Barnett earned her Bachelors from Texas State University with a major in Public Relations and a minor in Leadership in Communication. B was a statistics tutor at Texas State University and the founding President for Social Media Club Collegiate chapter. By pursuing the research side of public relations, B is able to explore the driving forces of successful campaigns.

B continued her education through her career by starting with a grass-roots company, HoneyMilk. As the forth hire, and the sole marketing department, B dug deep and figured out what would work to develop this amazing product into a national brand. Since then HoneyMilk rebranded as Core Power, part of the Fairlife brand. A brand now nationally distributed by Coca-Cola. She grew with the company from a Field Marketing Manager to a National Field Marketing Manager, and finally to a Special Initiatives Marketing Manager.

She insured all Field Marketing Managers across the country were trained for brand identity management, and lead large events of brand exposure. Such events and properties include: United States Olympic Commission, Fédération Internationale de Football Association, Spartan Race, Gladiator Rock'n Run, Rock'n'Roll Marathons, and all launches of Fairlife's emerging brands.

Since then B has emerged into the Texas Real Estate market, creating a homebuying and selling experience representative of the modern age.

Experience

Realtor for Reilly Realtors®

Dec 2010 - 2015

B dove into Real Estate and used her drive and marketing experience to create a business spanning DFW and ATX. She created systems and content to streamline other Realtor's business as well as her own.

Special Initiatives Marketing Manager, National Programs

Dec 2010 - 2015

As the Special Initiatives Marketing Manager, B leads the initiatives to create new programs on the field marketing level. Programs designed to facilitate the field marketing activations around major national and international properties and events.

Field Marketing for Red Bull North America

June 2008 - July 2009

Promoted the Red Bull brand through events and community excursions throughout Austin and the DFW area. Responsible for finding and creating activities that marketed the defined Red Bull brand.

District Manager, Marketing & Promotions for Darque Tan

May 2006 - May 2008

Managed and promoted six tanning salons across Austin and College Station. Worked to keep both the staff and the community educated on the benefits of tanning, and promoted the brand as a place of elegance and high standards.

Education

Texas State University--San Marcos - BA in Mass Communications -Summa Cum Laude, Golden Key Honors Society-

Graduate 2010

University of Westminster, London, England

Study Abroad 2010

University of Texas – Coding Bootcamp

Pursuing 2018